{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Satellite Dish Installation Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/40312/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40312,"taskName":"Satellite Dish System - Install","taskDescription":"Install a Satellite Dish System","xmTaskDescriptor":"Satellite Dish Installation Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":201,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"AV Dish equipment Satellite System","textMessagingName":"Satellite Dish","rolloverLongDesc":"Circular dishes varying in size from inches to yards that are used to receive \u0026 transmit signals to satellites orbiting the earth.","rolloverShortDesc":"Used for television \u0026 communications.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install a Satellite Dish System.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Satellite Dish Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Satellite TV","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":6,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Satellite Dish Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Satellite Dish System - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Satellite Dish System Project","urlName":"Satellite-Dish-System-Install","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Satellite Dish Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"AV,Satellite,System,visual,entertainment,network,directv,directtv,tv,direct,satelite,computer,audio","emcCategoryOid":-12006,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":612,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40312/":{"taskOID":40312,"originalTaskOID":40312,"setID":612,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4652,"questionDisplayText":"Location of satellite television","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you want satellite television? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3159,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In my single family residence","answerDisplayText":"In my single family residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3160,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In my single family residence under construction","answerDisplayText":"In my single family residence under construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3156,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"In my apartment or condominium","answerDisplayText":"In my apartment or condominium","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3157,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"In my apartment or condominium under construction","answerDisplayText":"In my apartment or condominium under construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3155,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"In my RV, sport utility vehicle, etc.","answerDisplayText":"In my RV, sport utility vehicle, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3158,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"In my boat","answerDisplayText":"In my boat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4653,"questionDisplayText":"Number of simultaneous stations","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many different TV stations would you like to be able to watch independently at the same time?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4367,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One","answerDisplayText":"One","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6545,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two","answerDisplayText":"Two","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6330,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three","answerDisplayText":"Three","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3947,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than three","answerDisplayText":"More than three","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4654,"questionDisplayText":"Type(s) of Programming","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of programming do you want? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3637,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Local stations","answerDisplayText":"Local stations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4128,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Networks","answerDisplayText":"Networks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5969,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sports channels","answerDisplayText":"Sports channels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4931,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Professional sports","answerDisplayText":"Professional sports","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6195,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Super stations","answerDisplayText":"Super stations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1227,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Cable stations","answerDisplayText":"Cable stations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4889,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Premium movie channels","answerDisplayText":"Premium movie channels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3361,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"International programming","answerDisplayText":"International programming","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4655,"questionDisplayText":"Special Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which of these special features would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6932,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Web TV","answerDisplayText":"Web TV","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1801,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"DVD Player","answerDisplayText":"DVD Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2900,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"HDTV (high definition television)","answerDisplayText":"HDTV (high definition television)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4133,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"New Dolby standard","answerDisplayText":"New Dolby standard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3057,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Home theater","answerDisplayText":"Home theater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5382,"questionDisplayText":"Purchased Satellite","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased a satellite dish?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":40001,"questionDisplayText":"Materials Provided by Homeowner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will you provide materials for this request?","shortQuestionText":"Homeowner to provide materials?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4652,"questionDisplayText":"Location of satellite television","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you want satellite television? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3159,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In my single family residence","answerDisplayText":"In my single family residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3160,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In my single family residence under construction","answerDisplayText":"In my single family residence under construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3156,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"In my apartment or condominium","answerDisplayText":"In my apartment or condominium","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3157,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"In my apartment or condominium under construction","answerDisplayText":"In my apartment or condominium under construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3155,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"In my RV, sport utility vehicle, etc.","answerDisplayText":"In my RV, sport utility vehicle, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3158,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"In my boat","answerDisplayText":"In my boat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3159,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In my single family residence","answerDisplayText":"In my single family residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3160,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In my single family residence under construction","answerDisplayText":"In my single family residence under construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3156,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"In my apartment or condominium","answerDisplayText":"In my apartment or condominium","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3157,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"In my apartment or condominium under construction","answerDisplayText":"In my apartment or condominium under construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3155,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"In my RV, sport utility vehicle, etc.","answerDisplayText":"In my RV, sport utility vehicle, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3158,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"In my boat","answerDisplayText":"In my boat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4653,"questionDisplayText":"Number of simultaneous stations","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many different TV stations would you like to be able to watch independently at the same time?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4367,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One","answerDisplayText":"One","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6545,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two","answerDisplayText":"Two","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6330,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three","answerDisplayText":"Three","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3947,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than three","answerDisplayText":"More than three","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4367,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One","answerDisplayText":"One","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6545,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two","answerDisplayText":"Two","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6330,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three","answerDisplayText":"Three","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3947,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than three","answerDisplayText":"More than three","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4654,"questionDisplayText":"Type(s) of Programming","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of programming do you want? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3637,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Local stations","answerDisplayText":"Local stations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4128,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Networks","answerDisplayText":"Networks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5969,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sports channels","answerDisplayText":"Sports channels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4931,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Professional sports","answerDisplayText":"Professional sports","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6195,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Super stations","answerDisplayText":"Super stations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1227,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Cable stations","answerDisplayText":"Cable stations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4889,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Premium movie channels","answerDisplayText":"Premium movie channels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3361,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"International programming","answerDisplayText":"International programming","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3637,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Local stations","answerDisplayText":"Local stations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4128,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Networks","answerDisplayText":"Networks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5969,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sports channels","answerDisplayText":"Sports channels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4931,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Professional sports","answerDisplayText":"Professional sports","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6195,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Super stations","answerDisplayText":"Super stations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1227,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Cable stations","answerDisplayText":"Cable stations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4889,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Premium movie channels","answerDisplayText":"Premium movie channels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3361,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"International programming","answerDisplayText":"International programming","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4655,"questionDisplayText":"Special Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which of these special features would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6932,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Web TV","answerDisplayText":"Web TV","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1801,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"DVD Player","answerDisplayText":"DVD Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2900,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"HDTV (high definition television)","answerDisplayText":"HDTV (high definition television)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4133,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"New Dolby standard","answerDisplayText":"New Dolby standard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3057,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Home theater","answerDisplayText":"Home theater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6932,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Web TV","answerDisplayText":"Web TV","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1801,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"DVD Player","answerDisplayText":"DVD Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2900,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"HDTV (high definition television)","answerDisplayText":"HDTV (high definition television)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4133,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"New Dolby standard","answerDisplayText":"New Dolby standard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3057,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Home theater","answerDisplayText":"Home theater","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5382,"questionDisplayText":"Purchased Satellite","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased a satellite dish?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":40001,"questionDisplayText":"Materials Provided by Homeowner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will you provide materials for this request?","shortQuestionText":"Homeowner to provide materials?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}